Like most of Canada, Vancouver and its area is extremely safe
像大多数加拿大城市一样，温哥华是一个安全系数很高的城市
Violent crimes are rare. However, like any large urban city
这里犯罪率很低，
petty crimes are common
偶尔会发生一些小型的犯罪
Areas such as downtown east side of Hasting street
像温哥华东部的Hasting街周围
are to be avoided walking late at night.
人们通常就会绕道而行
Transportation and taxis are generally very safe in Vancouver
温哥华的公共交通和出租车是非常安全的
and there are many apps used for navigating the cities.
学生在出行时可以借助导航软件查询路线
Students have many opportunities to familiarize themselves with Vancouver before exploring on their own
在学生独自探索这个城市之前，博域中学提供了充裕的机会让他们先熟悉温哥华的环境
as many of our weekend activities are held in and around the city
我们每个周末都会组织学生外出
led by our first-aid trained staff.
所有的活动也都是由有急救资质的老师带领的
Bodwell High School is located in the city of North Vancouver
博域位于北温哥华
just across the water on the north side of downtown.
和温哥华市中心隔水相望
North Vancouver is accessible from downtown by the seabus
平时学生出行可以乘坐Seabus
or by crossing the Lion's Gate bridge
或者经过狮门桥到达市中心
It is in a quiet neighbourhood at a roundabout corner
我们的学校位于一个安静的水湾处
with a pedestrian trail running along a sea wall at the back of the school
学校后面沿着海岸线是一条蜿蜒的小径
Students have their own free time after classes and clubs before their study hall and on weekends
每天在课程和社团活动结束后，自习开始前，学生都有一段自由活动时间
They are free to go out and explore
他们可以在这段时间安排自己的事情
but we ask them to swipe their key FOBs when they leave and return to the school
但是在他们进出学校时必须按照学校要求刷门禁卡
so staff is aware of their whereabouts.
以便我们的老师确定他们的在校情况，确保他们安全
For their safety outside the school, we conduct workshops
除此之外，为了保证他们外出时的安全，学校还会组织培训
to ensure they are aware how to avoid danger
确保孩子知道面对危险或是走失时
and what to do in the case of getting lost.
应该怎样处理
Students can call the school anytime - we are reachable 24 hours a day-
学生可以在任何时候拨打我们的24小时热线
use Google Maps, get a taxi,  or simply ask around
他们也可以利用谷歌地图，叫出租车或者询问路人
Canadians are generally very kind and willing to assist.
加拿大人民通常还是非常友好和乐于助人的
Students should exercise common sense when outside the school
学生可以通过外出活动获取生活常识
and not hesitate to call 911 if they find themselves in a dangerous or emergency situation.
在遇到危险或紧急状况时应该及时拨打911求助
Notifying friends or staff when leaving the campus is a good habit for students
出行前告知自己的朋友或家人自己的去向也是一个很好的习惯
At night, we require every student to follow curfew
学校要求每位学生遵守宵禁制度
and be back to their boarding by specific times for their safety
孩子们需要在宵禁前安全回到学校
All new students are assigned a locker
每一位新生入学的学生都有一个小储物柜
where they can put away or lock their valuables or personal items
他们可以将之前的个人物品存放在里面
It is not safe to leave valuables out in the open or in common areas
将个人物品留在公共区域是不安全的
During your child's stay here, they may get a bike, skateboard, rollerblade or other large equipment
在您的孩子在校期间他们可能会买单车，滑雪板，滑冰鞋等大的设备
The school has safe storage for these items
学校同时也为这些大型设备提供了储存空间
We also require them to adhere to the city's by-laws
我们也要求他们遵守交通规则
such as wearing a helmet while riding their bicycles and following traffic laws.
比如在骑行的时候要戴头盔等
School staff is here to assist your child in creating a safe, successful, memorable life here at Bodwell.
博域全体员工会尽心确保您的孩子在博域度过一个安全，成功，难忘的中学生活